<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Kalamazoo Vapor</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_juice_list">Juice List</string>
    <string name="title_activity_promotions">Promotion/!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_advanced_users">Advanced Users</string>
    <string name="title_activity_money_saver">Money Saver</string>
    <string name="title_activity_locations">Locations</string>
    <string name="title_activity_what_did_iget">What Did I Get/?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_information">Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_juice_tour">Juice Tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_juice_details">Juice Detail</string>
    <!-- String for juice list button -->
    <string name="btnJuiceList">Juice List</string>
    <!-- String for promotions button -->
    <string name="btnPromotions">Promotions</string>
    <!-- String for advanced users button -->
    <string name="btnAdvancedUsers">Advanced Users</string>
    <!-- String for information button -->
    <string name="btnInformation">Information</string>
    <!-- String for money saver button -->
    <string name="btnMoneySaver">Money Saver</string>
    <!-- String for locations button -->
    <string name="btnLocations">Locations</string>
    <!-- String for what did i get button -->
    <string name="btnWhatDidIGet">What Did I Get</string>
    <!-- String for juice tour button -->
    <string name="btnJuiceTour">Juice Tour</string>

    <string name="image_header">kzoo vapor logo</string>

    <!-- String for resistance calculator -->
    <string name="resistanceCalc">Resistance Calculator</string>
    <!-- String for wire type -->
    <string name="txtWireType">Wire Type</string>
    <!-- String for wire length -->
    <string name="txtWireLength">Length</string>
    <!-- String for wire gauge -->
    <string name="txtWireGauge">Gauge</string>
    <!-- String for diameter of coil -->
    <string name="txtDiameterOfCoil">Diameter of Coil</string>
    <!-- String for calculate button -->
    <string name="btnCalculate">Calculate</string>
    <!-- String for advanced user output -->
    <string name="txtCoilResistance">Your coil will have a resistance of:</string>
    <!-- String for unknown -->
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="SoFarSaved">Your savings are:</string>
    <string name="InitialCost">Inital Cost of Supplies</string>
    <string name="CostPerMil">Cost Per Millileter</string>
    <string name="AmountPerMil">Millileters</string>
    <string name="EJuicePerWeek">Amount of E-Juice Per Week</string>
    <string name="CostPerPack">Cost Per Pack</string>
    <string name="PacksPerWeek">Packs per week:</string>
    <string name="mnySaverImg">money saver image</string>
    <string name="imagedisc">holder for image</string>
    <string name="hintName">Name</string>
    <string name="hintManufacturer">Manufacturer</string>
    <color name="green">#8FD000</color>
    <color name="blue">#2F4CA3</color>

    <string-array name="houseJuiceArray">
        <item>Tastes like the apples and cinnamon cereal with slightly spicy tobacco notes.</item>
        <item>Tastes just like the popular soft drink that is exclusive to a well known fast-food
            taco restaurant. Little bit of citrus with a BLAST of berry.</item>
        <item>If you\'ve been looking for an energy drink flavor that is true to the original
            look no further this is it!</item>
        <item>Great Waffle taste!!</item>
        <item>A savory flavor for those who love the taste of blackberries.</item>
        <item>The one and only black licorice flavor</item>
        <item>Tastes like your favorite black and mild Cigar.</item>
        <item>The Blueberry flavor is a spot on fresh blueberry flavor. Our best seller in the fruit category.</item>
        <item>A delectable baked treat flavor.</item>
        <item>Ripe blueberries with a rich vanilla custard blended with our house tobacco base. Contains Custard notes.</item>
        <item>Ripe blueberries blended with a fresh, down-home lemonade flavor.</item>
        <item>You can almost hear the Ice Cream Man coming down the road as the Cherry, Lemon and
            Blue Raspberry tastes of this classic Popsicle flavor takes you back to your youth.</item>
        <item>A blend of Caramel, Banana, and Tobacco</item>
        <item>This Flavor is Vanilla cupcake topped with Butter Cream. Wow, is this one tasty! Contains Custard notes.</item>
        <item>Tastes just like the drink at the bar butter schnapps, irish cream and no bartender to tip.</item>
        <item>The timeless holiday classic peppermint candy.</item>
        <item>Like throwing a handful of these sweet, creamy autumnal treats in your mouth. This is
            a seasonal flavor that will only be offered for a limited time. Contains custard notes.</item>
        <item>Dark and Sweet, A Complex flavor of Creamy Caramel, fresh coconut, Vanilla, Rich Butterscotch,
            Sweet Coffee and just a hint of smooth tobacco. A true dessert tobacco unlike any other tobacco before it.</item>
        <item>Bright tart apple flavor with a creamy caramel undertone and a hint of mild tobacco.</item>
        <item>A baked treat flavor. Caramel blended with rich dark chocolate and toasted coconut.</item>
        <item>Great Tobacco flavor with a caramel tone. </item>
        <item>Rich cake batter, creamy vanilla custard and toasted marshmallow. The ultimate pawn killer.</item>
        <item>This is a great Cherry Cola Flavor one of my favorites.</item>
        <item>Just like the Cherry Tobacco your Grandpa use to Smoke out of his old pipe.</item>
        <item>A twist of cherry and vanilla.</item>
        <item>Rich, dark chocolate blended with a sweet, bright cherry flavor.</item>
        <item>It doesn\'t get any closer to the flavor of a premium clove cigarette than this!</item>
        <item>Tastes like a refreshing cola.</item>
        <item>A creamy blend of different berries.</item>
        <item>Cool Shots add menthol to any of the flavors below, available in THREE levels\n
        Cool - barely mentholated\nFrosted - medium menthol\nFrozen - you will just about see your breath\n
        \nBlackberry, Blueberry, Juicy Peach, Laffy Laffy Banana, Pear, Raspberry, Raspberry Vanilla Twist,
         Strawberry, Strawberry Lemonade, Tango Mango and Wacky Watermelon</item>
        <item>Cybermint is a blend of mint and menthol, with a slight sweet finish. kinda like those round mints.</item>
        <item>Smooth butterscotch and rich chocolate with just a hint of creamy coffee will have you craving the Dark Side for eternity.</item>
        <item>Ripe mixed berries blended with a smooth, sweeter tobacco.</item>
        <item>Crisp citrus blended with sweet pomegranate</item>
        <item>Like walking into Granny\'s house during the holidays. The taste of fresh baked apple pie.</item>
        <item>That great Grape Drink flavor that is clear not purple!</item>
        <item>Rich, dark chocolate blended with a creamy mint.</item>
        <item>Crisp, tart apple flavor</item>
        <item>The great taste of Gummi Bears!!!</item>
        <item>This flavor is reminiscent of that red gum we loved so much as a kid. BIG and Red on
            flavor. Intense cinnamon candy flavor with a light fruity kick.</item>
        <item>This is a smooth, flavorful butterscotch cappuccino flavor.</item>
        <item>Tastes like a Georgia Peach.</item>
        <item>This is our energy drink flavor!!</item>
        <item>Tastes just like that bazooka flavor gum from when i was a kid. </item>
        <item>That famous treat from the Conch Republic. Creamy Key Lime flavor with a graham crackery shell.</item>
        <item>That great taste of the center of your favorite long john donut. </item>
        <item>A nice Blend of RY4 and 555 with a little something extra.</item>
        <item>This is by far the Best 555 Flavor that i have come across in my search. </item>
        <item>This is a semi clear coffee flavor kinda like a cappuccino.</item>
        <item>A Standard Menthol Tobacco Flavor.</item>
        <item>KVS Version of Ry4 Tobacco Flavor. </item>
        <item>A Menthol Tobacco flavor with a hint of chocolate.</item>
        <item>Our solid standard for a tobacco flavor.</item>
        <item>Tastes just like those little banana candies.</item>
        <item>The cornerstone of our lemonade line. Fresh, tart, sweet... just as it should be.</item>
        <item>This is the same flavor that Gene from Mad Hatter Cig sold he gave me the mix to sell.
            It is a nice smooth tobacco flavor with a kick of sweet to it. </item>
        <item>A cross between Mellow Yellow and Mountain Dew flavor.</item>
        <item>Menthol, Like an arctic kick in the face. Not minty just menthol and lots of it.</item>
        <item>Michigan is known as the "mitten state" Mitten Juice is a tasty blend of two of
            Michigan\'s top produced fruit crops, Apples and Strawberries.</item>
        <item>A flavorful tropical energy drink flavor.</item>
        <item>KVS Flagship Tobacco Flavor. Our number one selling tobacco flavor. A complex,
            yet smooth blend of different 14 different tobacco flavors.</item>
        <item>Tastes like an orange smoothie or sherbet.</item>
        <item>A sweet, fruity drink flavor with all the tastes of the islands.</item>
        <item>Fresh Pear Flavor.</item>
        <item>This flavor is just like the drink.</item>
        <item>The taste of the king of tropical fruits.</item>
        <item>Rich ice cream combined with sweet almonds and nutty pistachios.</item>
        <item>Fresh raspberry flavor</item>
        <item>Another great addition to our lemonade line, this time with ripe raspberries.</item>
        <item>A creamy blend of fresh, ripe raspberries and premium vanilla flavors.</item>
        <item>This is a great Root Beer with a little float. </item>
        <item>Rich chocolate blended with sweet marshmallow, topped off with a graham cracker finish.</item>
        <item>Best Strawberry that we have found by far!!!</item>
        <item>A refreshingly crisp drink flavor combining fresh, ripe strawberries and the lemonade
            your grandma used to make.</item>
        <item>A smooth creamy blend of fresh strawberries and one of the best colada flavors we
            could find. The only thing missing is the umbrella and fancy straw.</item>
        <item>A nice blend of Strawberry and Kiwi flavors for a great vape.</item>
        <item>Strawberries and Bananas, \'nuff said!</item>
        <item>Tasty blend of ripe strawberries and juicy peaches.</item>
        <item>A refreshingly sweet blend of lemon, lime and tangerine.</item>
        <item>This well known candy flavor blends sweet with sour.</item>
        <item>A nice blend of fresh peach and ripe mango flavors. </item>
        <item>Tastes like the classic Striped Gum but retains its flavor much longer.</item>
        <item>Our customers have been asking for a Turkish style tobacco and we have delivered.
            This is a clean European-style turkish blend tobacco flavor.</item>
        <item>This is a Vanilla flavor with Mint not Menthol.</item>
        <item>A great blend of Tobacco and Vanilla.</item>
        <item>This is a killer Cherry Flavor. </item>
        <item>A complex blend of vine ripened strawberries with fresh, juicy peaches and sweetly tart lemon.</item>
        <item>This flavor tastes just like a Jolly Rancher candy.</item>
        <item>This is a smooth straight tobacco flavor. </item>
        <item>This tobacco is a blend of tobacco, menthol, vanilla and mint. </item>
        <item>This mentholated Watermelon Lemonade is reminiscent to a snow cone flavor. No huskies
            were harmed in the making of this flavor</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
